hello good people bring the promise
[Music]
insurance
Z steps in choosing the right life
policy needs evaluate your financial gos
income and needs to determine the
appropriate coverage and amount policy
number two research explore the
different life insurance policies
comping the features benefits and
premium general
costs
okay and
then
understand is only 8 years old hi I want
to be a lawyer do you know how much it
costs Grace To Go to a university I
think it's 500,000 Shillings I'm afraid
it's a lot more than that and the only
way great parents can afford the costs
is if they start saving today with Pro
Ed you save and Prudential will make
sure Grace goes to University with over
24 million customers worldwide and over
169 years of existence your child's
education is guaranteed with credential
talk to us today and let's face life
together T credential Insurance ug
Li
secondary I mean
primary
yeah
so
yes
[Music]
protection and savings return investment
return
okay what
2033 is when it will mature in December
but what is the value it's going to pay
50 million that is 100% of the Su
insured
then rary
bonuses
17.1
995 so that is 17.1 million and this is
at a rate
of% 50
million time
1.3% 53
million
uh
1.3
element
0.3 yeah *
1.03
1.3 simply like
thats the quation is for illustrative
purposes only the results are just
estimates bonus rates are declared
annually for policies that are pay their
premiums and the bonus rate used for
calculating the estimates is 3% so
illustration
bonus
calculating then maturity three equal
installments with no additional
bonuses 7 67
million dividing into three
so 22.3
million I mean
after estimate that is
bonus
or permanent and total disability
benefit premium applies in the event of
death 4
15,000 monthly premium
yes
disability
50% then
benefits illust
purp whatever you have
got
[Music]
milus so that is
45,1 184
th000 is what you are paying per month
so remember it's very
important how much you're putting in Vis
how much you're getting out so here we
seeing that um per month in a year would
have paid 4.9
millions of course in 10 years you would
have accumulated 49.8 million so what
they guaranteeing you on this 49.8
million you would have contributed
you have a return of
about uh
81 9 let's just round it up so that's
about 17.3
million
return conservative
rate so meaning if these bonuses have
been given declared every
year
bonuses of that money but of course the
Su
insured is what applies mostly in the
contract but you have to take note that
the companies have to declare these
bonuses on a yearly basis because
inv there are also
claims
policy
extensions war and related
perals police
extension then
AVI or 33% of the 50
million
that is what you would have
contributed you would have contri about
9.8 million at the end of the 10 years
how much you would have accumulated for
this particular policy but if we are to
use this same
example uh for someone paying annually
or semiannually of course their
discounted rates
meaning all other things will remain the
same
4.8
165 times
bonus with bonuses you're looking at
about sorry at
about let's just round it up you're
looking at about 18 million
so
is this keyx document it's very
important it illustrates very very
finely what your policy should look like
and this is now a new development from
the regulator that you have to have this
key facts document for you to understand
and summarize for you what this policy
is all about
so
docents
the parent or grandar takes out the
policy to provide the children's
education of
course decide the amount of contribution
and we calculate the sum insured all the
so suured
Cate premium or contribution the amount
that shall be payable either on death of
polic of the policy holder or at the Sur
of the policy
tered value in you decide for how long
you want like to save the period between
5 to 20 years minimum premium is 100,000
per month so
contract
exclusions
examples
80%
depending on the
[Music]
period
Destin we all work together as one
[Music]
com to real
isal our values me alone we are the
people who give it
[Applause]
all reason to
believe we are number
one we are number
one take one more
St Reach Out For
Excellence we'll do whatever it takes to
touch
thisy and we help each other reach our
aspir we know that we can do it if we
St we are
predal our values me Al we are the
people have a valent reason to
believe we are number
one we are number one
we are number one number
one one we are one
one one one
one number
one